<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga</string>
    <string name="_1_assume_a_face_down_prone_position_on_the_floor_keep_your_feet_together_your_weight_should_be_on_your_chest_position_hands_palms_down_on_the_floor_approximately_shoulder_width_apart_they_should_be_about_next_to_your_shoulders_with_your_elbows_pointed_towards_your_toes_if_you_are_on_a_relatively_cushioned_surface_such_as_a_carpeted_floor_you_may_also_support_yourself_on_your_fists_between_the_first_and_second_knuckles_for_a_greater_challenge_if_you_are_on_a_less_forgiving_surface_consider_investing_in_some_push_up_grips_they_look_like_handles_you_put_on_the_floor_curl_your_toes_upward_towards_your_head_the_balls_of_your_feet_should_touch_the_ground_2_raise_yourself_using_your_arms_at_this_point_your_weight_should_be_supported_by_your_hands_and_the_balls_of_your_feet_make_a_straight_line_from_your_head_to_your_heels_and_contract_your_abdominals_to_keep_your_hips_from_sagging_this_position_is_called_a_plank_which_is_used_for_various_exercises_this_is_the_beginning_and_the_end_position_of_a_single_push_up">1. Assume a face-down prone position on the floor. Keep your feet together. Your weight should be on your chest. Position hands palms-down on the floor, approximately shoulder-width apart. They should be about next to your shoulders, with your elbows pointed towards your toes. If you are on a relatively cushioned surface, such as a carpeted floor, you may also support yourself on your fists between the first and second knuckles for a greater challenge. If you are on a less forgiving surface, consider investing in some push-up grips, (they look like handles you put on the floor). Curl your toes upward (towards your head). The balls of your feet should touch the ground. 2. Raise yourself using your arms. At this point, your weight should be supported by your hands and the balls of your feet. Make a straight line from your head to your heels, and contract your abdominals to keep your hips from sagging. This position is called a plank, which is used for various exercises. This is the beginning and the end position of a single push up.</string>
    <string name="push">push</string>
    <string name="monday_detail_activity">Monday detail activity</string>
</resources>